ABDULLAH AL MAMUN

7/4 Boshoti Housing, Borobagh,

Mirpur-2, Dhaka- 1216 Contact: +8801734256807

Email: almamun0105@gmail.com



Career Objective:

Highly motivated Human Resource specialist seeking a human resource position in a fast paced organization where excellent planning and management skills will be fully utilized.

Career Summary:

Professional, people-first HR manager with 5+ years in human resources division jobs and comfortable with taking the lead in employment protocol compliance and in anticipating staffing needs with trained in non-profit settings.

Employment History: Total Year of Experience: 5 Year's.

JAAGO Foundation

Sr. Officer (1st January 2017 - Continuing)

Company Location: Banani

Department: Human Resource Department



Duties/Responsibilities:

- Management of HRIS Database.
- Assist in planning and implementing the action plan and strategy of Human Resource Division.
- Assist in workforce planning, budgeting and designing organizational structures of Human Resource Division.
- Work as a focal person for all communication-related activities of Human Resource Division.
- Schedule and organize different meetings, conferences, workshops of Human Resource Division.
- Work closely with the HR strategy team to bring in positive cultural changes in the organization.
- Involve with Safeguarding Responsibilities.
- Develop compensation and benefits plans.
- Support and suggest improvements to the entire recruitment process.
- Review departmental budgets.
- Organize learning and development programs.
- Exercise and maintain a high degree of confidentiality.

JAAGO Foundation

Communication Officer (15th October, 2015 -29th December, 2016)

Company Location: Banani

Department: Youth Development Program



Duties/Responsibilities:

- Establish a good relationship with concern District.
- Encourage volunteer engagement with social responsibilities.
- Communicate with volunteers from each District regularly.
- Filing meeting munities, event report, and project proposal of volunteer groups.
- Preserve and promote Volunteer for Bangladesh among Districts.
- Operate & monitor concern Districts social media.
- Organize new project from District.
- Empower Divisional board & engage them for develop every District.
- Make a plan for every District according to the attitude & environment of that District.
- Find out the problem & solution in every District.
- Make a report regarding on District status and submit it at the end of every month.
- Give emphasis & take initiative for the development of volunteer.
- Plan, Organize and Monitoring the National Project.

Tiger Tours & Travels

Jr. Executive (1st January, 2014 – 31st December, 2014)

Company Location: Gulshan

Department: Human Resource Department



Al Arafa Islami Bank

Intern (29th August, 2013 – 31st December, 2013)

Company Location: Panthapath Department: General Banking



Training Summary:

Training Title	Institute	Year	Duration
KPI Based Performance Management System	United International University Career Counseling Center	2019	1 Day
Labor Law	Bangladesh Institute of Human Resource Management	2018	2 Days
Employee Recruitment & Selection Process	Bdjobs	2018	1 Day
Employee Learning, Training & Development	Bdjobs	2017	2 Days



Academic Qualification:

Exam Title	Major	Institute	Result	Pas.Year
Post Graduate Diploma (PGD)	Human Resource Management	Bangladesh Institute of Management (BIM)	CGPA:3.86 out of 4	2019
Master of Business Administration (MBA)	Human Resource Management	BRAC University	CGPA:3.07 out of 4	2017
Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)	Human Resource Management	Stamford University Bangladesh	CGPA:3.42 out of 4	2013
Higher Secondary School Certificate (HSC)	Business Studies	Narikel Baria Degree Collage, Jessore	CGPA:4.60 out of 5	2009
Secondary School Certificate (SSC)	Business Studies	Narikel Baria High School, Jessore	CGPA:3.88 out of 5	2007

Professional Qualification:

Certification	Institute	Location	Duration
Bangladesh- Srilanka Youth Exchange Program	National Youth Services Council (NYSC)	Srilanka	11 Days
Good Governance & Capacity Building	JAAGO Foundation	Sylhet	2 Days
Ignite Deep Drive	Bangladesh Youth Leadership Center (BYLC)	Dhanmondi	2 Days

Past Experience & Achievement:

- Most Punctual Employee 2019 at JAAGO
- Popular Employee of the year 2018 at JAAGO
- Best Team Player of the year 2018 at JAAGO
 Best employee of the month 3rd times at JAAG

Reference:

Name : Md. Faysal Siddiqui Mamun Rashid Organization : JAAGO Foundation **BRAC** University

Designation : Deputy Manager Professor

Mobile : +8801615694343 +8801711525428

E-Mail : faisal.sidduqui@jaago.com.bd mamun.rashid@bracu.com.bd

Relation : Professional Academic